



Hybrid designer & full-stack developer with a penchant for clean, succint visual solutions. My background in advertising and holistic approach to brand identity ensures a user experience that's as usable as it is compelling.



# **Projects**

### **Beacon**

I worked with a fellow General Assembly student to create an Angular web application that leverages Google Maps API and Seattle police report data with one goal: to help you figure out the safest way to get from one place to another in Seattle.

### M.E.A.N. Coach

Collaboration with two other student developers at General Assembly to design and develop and web app for tracking daily calories. The app utilizes a full M.E.A.N. JavaScript stack, allowing users to set daily calorie goals, search the USDA API for foods, track exercises, and save daily logs to make sure their fitness goals stay on track.

### AT&T SPARK

In winter of 2015 I developed a UI and UX web application for AT&T's Big Data division. The purpose of this interactive tool is to present rich consumer analytics related to event marketing. My role was to determine the site structure, consider the optimal methods of data presentation, and create an interface design consistent with the AT&T brand.

### **Netflix Originals Marketing**

I've worked on multiple international launches for Netflix, helping them introduce their service offering through a coordinated range of digital marketing and point-of-sale pieces. My role was to art direct brand collateral and manage the design of individual TV series campaigns to ensure consistency of communication across four continents.

### Hashtag Hustle

I helped develop a social media contest for Spokane Hoopfest, the largest 3-on-3 basket-ball tournament in the world. The contest awarded users points for completing a variety of basketball-related tasks. My job was to figure out how the contest worked and create an over-arching style that suited the inherently silly nature of the competition.



### **Skills** (In order of relative competency)

### DESIGN

Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe InDesign, InVision, Marvel

### DEVELOPMENT

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, Python Frameworks: AngularJS, React, Node.js, Express, Django Libraries: jQuery, Bootstrap\* Databases/ORM: Sequelize, PostgresSQL, MongoDB Other: AJAX, Git, Heroku

<sup>\*</sup> Though I prefer to do CSS styling by hand.



## **Education**

## **General Assembly**

Web Developent Immersive • 2017 Certificate, Front-End Development • 2016

### Savannah College of Art & Design

BFA, Graphic Design • 2008 Graduated summa cum laude



## Experience

### Freelance Brand Designer

Self-Employed • Seattle, WA March 2016—Present

### Designer

Chapter & Verse • Seattle, WA June 2012—February 2016

### **Adjunct Instructor: Advertising Concepts**

Eastern Washington University • Cheney, WA January 2014—March 2014

### **Art Director**

BHW1 • Spokane, WA August 2010—June 2012

### **Junior Designer**

Kaleidoscope • Chicago, IL February 2009—May 2010

### **Design Intern**

UNIT partners • San Francisco, CA September 2008—November 2008



## Recognition

### **Webby Awards**

Honoree (2014): AmericanWest Bank Website

### **Inland Northwest ADDY Awards**

Silver (2013): Visit Spokane Identity Silver (2012): BHW1 Christmas Coasters

### **Spokane ADDY Awards**

Best of Show (2012): BHW1 Christmas Coasters